<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!DOCTYPE game SYSTEM "game.dtd">
<game name="Project">
	<script begin="sc_1">
		<script-node id="sc_1">
			<child child-id="sc_2"/>
		</script-node>
		<script-node id="sc_2">
			<child child-id="sc_3"/>
		</script-node>
		<script-node id="sc_3">
			<child child-id="sc_4"/>
			<child child-id="sc_5"/>
			<child child-id="sc_6"/>
		</script-node>
		<script-node id="sc_4">
			<child child-id="sc_7"/>
		</script-node>
		<script-node id="sc_5">
			<child child-id="sc_7"/>
		</script-node>
		<script-node id="sc_6">
			<child child-id="sc_8"/>
		</script-node>
		<script-node id="sc_7">
			<child child-id="sc_8"/>
		</script-node>
		<script-node id="sc_8">
			<child child-id="sc_9"/>
			<child child-id="sc_10"/>
			<child child-id="sc_11"/>
			<child child-id="sc_12"/>
		</script-node>
		<script-node id="sc_9">
			<child child-id="sc_13"/>
			<child child-id="sc_16"/>
		</script-node>
		<script-node id="sc_10">
			<child child-id="sc_18"/>
		</script-node>
		<script-node id="sc_11">
			<child child-id="sc_17"/>
		</script-node>
		<script-node id="sc_12">
			<child child-id="sc_18"/>
		</script-node>
		<script-node id="sc_13">
			<child child-id="sc_14"/>
		</script-node>
		<script-node id="sc_14"/>
		<script-node id="sc_15">
			<child child-id="sc_18"/>
		</script-node>
		<script-node id="sc_16">
			<child child-id="sc_17"/>
			<child child-id="sc_18"/>
		</script-node>
		<script-node id="sc_17">
			<child child-id="sc_18"/>
		</script-node>
		<script-node id="sc_18">
			<child child-id="sc_19"/>
		</script-node>
		<script-node id="sc_19">
		</script-node>
	</script>
	<map begin="Amphitheater">
		<location id="Amphitheater">
			<name>Amphitheater</name>
			<text>Teacher : Blah blah blah... project... \n Your eyes are fluttering. Fatigue inavdes you. Slowly, the room around you disappears. You must recognize that Jovo's classes have never been your strength....as evidenced by your grades in the last test. You feel your eyelids become heavier and heavier \n - BAM ! \n You make up with a start ! Around you, the students have already started to leave the amphitheater. It was their noisy discussionsthat got you out of sleep. Very quickly, you are the only one still sitting. The teacher glares at you from his desk. He propably wants to go on a lunch break or maybe he noticed that you slept the entire lecture... You look away. \n On your right, you notice a young long-haired girl who are smiling at you. On your left, there is a bearded boy hypnotised by his phone. The exit of the amphitheater are calling you : it's the freedom's door. You finally decide to get up.
			</text>
			<desc>It is a place where the students assist to their lecture. It is also a cold place without any warmth.</desc>
			<door id="door1" to="Hall"/>
		</location>
		<location id="Hall">
			<name>Hall</name>
			<text>You are in the main place of the game : the hall of the building
			</text>
			<desc>It is a place where the students wait for their classes. They also can drink coffee at the coffee machine.
			</desc>
			<door id="door2" to="Amphitheater"/>
			<door id="door3" to="Classroom"/>
			<door id="door4" to="Secretary"/>
			<door id="door5" to="SmokerZone"/>
		</location>
		<location id="Classroom">
			<name>Classroom</name>
			<text>You enter in the classroom. Maria, as the perfect student, is sitting in the first row. She is ready for the beginning of the class. Hurry up it will starts in few minutes.
			</text>
			<desc>In the classroom, the students can assist to classes and learn new things.
			</desc>
			<door id="door6" to="Hall"/>
		</location>
		<location id="Secretary">
			<name>Secretary's office</name>
			<text>You are in the secretary's office. Talk with the secretary if you need anything.
			</text>
			<desc>If you need informations or health's points, you can come here. The secretary will be happy to help you if you ask her politely of course...
			</desc>
			<door id="door7" to="Hall"/>
		</location>
		<location id="SmokerZone">
			<name>Smoker Zone</name>
			<text>You are in the smoker zone. Be careful at your lungs !</text>
			<desc>The students who smoke come here. At every break, this place is full of toxic smoke...
			</desc>
			<door id="door8" to="Hall"/>
			<door id="door9" to="SecretRoom"/>
		</location>
		<location id="SecretRoom">
			<name>Secret Room</name>
			<text>You are in the secret room. Good luck leaving this scary place... \n The only way to exit it is to use the precious key. If you do not have it then your life won't be long...
			</text>
			<desc>It is a secret place somewhere...</desc>
			<door id="door10" to="Hall" key="key"/>
		</location>
	</map>
	<items-list>
		<item id="Hpts">
			<name>Health point</name>
			<desc/>
		</item>
		<item id="key">
			<name>The Key</name>
			<desc>This is the only key to escape from the room.</desc>
		</item>
		<item id="sheet">
			<name>Project's sheet</name>
			<desc>The project contains 4 sheets.</desc>
		</item>
	</items-list>
	<characters-list>
		<character id="Teacher1" location="Amphitheater">
			<name>Teacher of your project</name>
			<desc/>
			<dialog id="T_dia1" begin="T1_1" available="sc_1"><dialog-node id="T1_1"><text>The closer you get to him, the more nasty his look becomes...It's a bad idea. You turn around.</text></dialog-node>
			</dialog>
			<dialog id="T_dia2" begin="T2_1_1" available="sc_2"><dialog-node id="T2_1_1"><text>Teacher : What about your papers, young man ! You have to listen in lecture.</text><answer redirect="T2_2_2">Take the document.</answer></dialog-node><dialog-node id="T2_2_2" execute="giveitem sheet"><text>You go down the amphitheater and take the document on the teacher's desk. It describes exactly the differents steps of the project : you are learning that you must find a partner. You immediately start to find one. \n The teacher leaves the amphitheater by grumbling something about the students these days... \n You have one sheet in your possession and you need 4 to complete the project.</text></dialog-node>
			</dialog>
			<dialog id="T_dia3" begin="T3_1" available="sc_18"><dialog-node id="T3_1"><text>Teacher : blah blah blah.... \n Now I will /* ramasser */ your project. Put them on my desk. \n You stand up and take the project in your hands. You read it briefly while you go down the stairs. Your hands start to shake. You are not sure about this project... You look around, your partner Maki is not here so you can not ask him his opinion. What can you do ?</text><answer redirect="T3_2">/* rendre le project */</answer><answer redirect="T3_3">Keep it</answer></dialog-node><dialog-node id="T3_2"><text>You give your project to the teacher. You really hope to have a good mark because you work so hard on it. After leaving your project on his desk, you leave the amphitheater with finger crossed.</text></dialog-node><dialog-node id="T3_3"><text>You decide to keep it. After all, the teacher won't be mad if you give it to him tomorrow... This day /* supplémentaire*/ will let you /* perfectionner */ your project \n Teacher : I forgot to tell you, if you do not give me your project today then you will get a 0. \n Maybe you will re-think about give it now or not...</text><answer redirect="T3_2">/* rendre your project */</answer><answer>Keep it for good</answer></dialog-node>
			</dialog>
		</character>
		<character id="Teacher2" location="Classroom">
			<name>Teacher</name>
			<desc/>
			<dialog id="T2_dia2" begin="T2_1" available="sc_10"><dialog-node id="T2_1"><text>You decide to assist to the class. It will denefits you. You are sure of that. \n Except Maria sitting in the first row, the other chairs are empty. \n Where do you want to sit ?</text><answer redirect="T2_2">Sit in the first row</answer><answer redirect="T2_3">Sit in the middle row</answer><answer redirect="T2_4">Sit in the last row</answer></dialog-node><dialog-node id="T2_2"><text>You chose to sit in the first row, this is a good choice. It will allow you to get every information the teacher will give. The chair next to Maria is empty... \n You : Hey Maria ! Can I sit next to you ? \n Maria : Of course you can ! It has been so long since our last conversation... \n - Yeah I know... By the way, I wanted to apologize to you for changing my project's partner... \n - Do not be worried about this, I am not mad at you or at least not anymore... Besides, I found a project's partner so I am not alone... \n Maria smiles at you. You are truly relieve that Maria do not *t'en vouloir* anymore. \n Now you can completely focus on the lesson... \n \n Teacher : The class will starts in a few minutes. For the students who do not want to be there then I will ask you to leave the classroom and for the others then I will ask you to stop the chatting... \n</text><answer redirect="T2_5">Stay focus on the entire class</answer></dialog-node><dialog-node id="T2_3"><text>You chose to sit in the middle row, maybe this is not the best choice but you did not want to sit in the first row... The teacher would have been to close to you... \n You are not worried, you will still be focus on the class... for sure ... for 80 per cents sure... \n Teacher : The class will starts in a few minutes. For the students who do not want to be there then I will ask you to leave the classroom and for the others then I will ask you to stop the chatting... \n</text><answer redirect="T2_5">Stay focus on the entire class</answer><answer redirect="T2_6">/* partir dans ses pensées</answer></dialog-node><dialog-node id="T2_4"><text>You chose to sit in the last row. Behind others, the teacher will not see you and you will be able to do everything except listen to him... \n Teacher : The class will starts in a few minutes. For the students who do not want to be there then I will ask you to leave the classroom and for the others then I will ask you to stop the chatting... \n</text><answer redirect="T2_6">Try to stay focus on the class</answer></dialog-node><dialog-node id="T2_5" execute="giveitem sheet"><text>You succeeded to stay focus on the class. Every information given by the teacher were caught by your brain. You are pride of yourself and you were right to assist to it because it was very benefit for you. \n Teacher : The class is finished but before exit, I give you a paper useful for your project. \n You received another page to complete your project. Assisted to the class was definitely a good thing for you !</text></dialog-node><dialog-node id="T2_6"><text>The class is finally finished... You tried to stay focus but you have to admit that your sight was more outside throught the window than focus on the black board in front of you. You caught some information about a paper given by the teacher but when you realized the class was over, the teacher was already gone. Let's hope you won't regret it later...</text></dialog-node>
			</dialog>
		</character>
		<character id="Maria1" location="Amphitheater">
			<name>Maria</name>
			<desc>She is a beautiful long-haired girl and you are lucky, she is in the same class than you.</desc>
			<dialog id="M_dia1" begin="M1_1" available="sc_1 sc_2"><dialog-node id="M1_1"><text>Long-haired girl : Hello ! My name is Maria. I saw that you were sleeping during class. You should go to see the teacher for the explanations that you missed.</text></dialog-node>
			</dialog>
			<dialog id="M_dia2" begin="M2_1" available="sc_3 sc_4"><dialog-node id="M2_1"><text>Maria : Do you have a pair for the project ? Otherwise we could get together if you want.</text><answer redirect="M2_2">Accept her proposition</answer><answer redirect="M2_3">Reject her proposition</answer></dialog-node><dialog-node id="M2_2"><text>Maria smiles at you and you have the impression that the entire universe is contained in her dimples.\n She takes your hand. \n Maria : I am really happy that you want to work with me ! \n It is your turn to blush. Embarrased, you tell her that you are happy too. Maria smiles at you again. You decide to leave the amphitheater together and come back home. You live next to each other, so why not make the way together ?... \n Suddenly, a young man approch you with a nice smile on his face. \n Young man : Hey classmate. I was wondering, do you have a partner for the project ?.... Because if you do not have one then we can be together... \n After his long and non-sense speech, your head is turning. \n</text><answer redirect="M2_5">Accept his proposition</answer><answer redirect="M2_4">Refuse his proposition</answer></dialog-node><dialog-node id="M2_3"><text>You are alone and you read the project again... You absolutely need a partner.</text></dialog-node><dialog-node id="M2_4"><text>What !? You do not want to be with me... Why ?...</text><answer redirect="M2_5">I already have a partner</answer><answer redirect="M2_5">I do not want to be with you</answer><answer redirect="M2_6">I was joking. Let's do the project together</answer></dialog-node><dialog-node id="M2_5"><text>Come on, it will be fun. Are you really sure you do not want to be with me ?</text><answer redirect="M2_4">Yes</answer><answer redirect="M2_6">No</answer></dialog-node><dialog-node id="M2_6"><text>You accept Maki's proposition. Maki hugs you and tells you see you tomorrow. Here is someone who will make a reliable partner. Happy with yourself, you go home whistling.</text></dialog-node>
			</dialog>
		</character>
		<character id="Zack1" location="Amphitheater">
			<name>Zack</name>
			<desc>He is a bearded man in the same class than you.</desc>
			<dialog id="Z_dia1" begin="Z1_1" available="sc_1 sc_2"><dialog-node id="Z1_1"><text>Bearded man : Hi ! I am Zack. How was your nap ?</text></dialog-node>
			</dialog>
			<dialog id="Z_dia2" begin="Z2_1" available="sc_3 sc_5"><dialog-node id="Z2_1"><text>Do you want to be my partner for the project ?</text><answer redirect="Z2_2">Accept his proposition</answer><answer redirect="Z2_3">Reject his proposition</answer></dialog-node><dialog-node id="Z2_2"><text>You accept his proposition. He seems to be happy. Immediately, he goes to join his friends and disappears from your sight. You try to follow him but he was faster than you and you lost him. You will propably never see him again and accept his proposition was a terrible mistake. \n Suddenly, a young man approch you with a nice smile on his face. \n Young man : You should not have accepted his proposition ! He won't do anything on the project and you are going to do everything by yourself. Come with me. Besides, I already did a similar project so it is going to be so easy. \n - Oh... I am Maki by the way.</text><answer redirect="Z2_4">Accept his proposition</answer><answer redirect="Z2_4">Accept Maki's proposition</answer></dialog-node><dialog-node id="Z2_3"><text>You are alone and you read the project again... You absolutely need a partner.</text></dialog-node><dialog-node id="Z2_4"><text>You accept Maki's proposition and you are so happy to be free from Zack. Maki hugs you and tells you see you tomorrow. Here is someone who will make a reliable partner. Happy with yourself, you go home whistling.</text></dialog-node>
			</dialog>
		</character>
		<character id="Zack2" location="SmokerZone">
			<name>Zack</name>
			<desc/>
			<dialog id="Z2_dia2" begin="Z3_1" available="sc_9 sc_16"><dialog-node id="Z3_1"><text>You are seeing Zack in the smoker zone. You come closer to him with the hope that maybe he knows where are the missing pages. \n Zack : I have nothing to tell you...</text></dialog-node>
			</dialog>
		</character>
		<character id="Maki1" location="Amphitheater">
			<name>Maki</name>
			<desc/>
			<dialog id="Mk_dia1" begin="Mk1_1" available="sc_6"><dialog-node id="Mk1_1"><text>You go out the amphitheater and you arrive in the hall of the building. A lots of students are chatting. You will find a partner here. As soon as this thought comes in your mind, a young man who seems to be a little bit too excited approch you : \n Young man : Hey classmate. I was wondering, do you have a partner for the project ?.... Because if you do not have one then we can be together. \n After his long and non-sense speech, your head is turning. You do not know if it is due to the smoke of his electronic cigarette or due to the lots of information he gave you. You finally understand that he want to be your project partner.</text><answer redirect="Mk1_2">Accept his proposition</answer><answer redirect="Mk1_1">Refuse his proposition</answer></dialog-node><dialog-node id="Mk1_2"><text>You accept Maki's proposition with a confused mind. After this, he leaves the building. You decide to go home to take a rest. After all, your mission to find a partner was a success so you can have a little break.</text></dialog-node>
			</dialog>
		</character>
		<character id="Maki2" location="SmokerZone">
			<name>Maki</name>
			<desc/>
			<dialog id="Mk_dia2" begin="Mk2_1" available="sc_9"><dialog-node id="Mk2_1"><text>Maki is in the smoker zone as always, you come closer to him. \n Maki : What's up dude ? \n You : Good \n</text><answer redirect="Mk2_2">Leave the conversation</answer><answer redirect="Mk2_3">Did you work on the project ?</answer></dialog-node><dialog-node id="Mk2_2"><text>Maki : Okay see you later then</text></dialog-node><dialog-node id="Mk2_3"><text>Maki : Yeah do not be worried about this. \n You : I'm serious... Maki : I did not start yet but trust me I will work on it soon.</text><answer redirect="Mk2_3">Yell at him</answer><answer redirect="Mk2_5">Okay I trust you</answer></dialog-node><dialog-node id="Mk2_5"><text>Maki : You should go to see the secretary, I heard that she might have a paper to complete our project...</text></dialog-node>
			</dialog>
		</character>
		<character id="Maki3" location="SmokerZone">
			<name>Maki</name>
			<desc/>
			<dialog id="Mk_dia3" begin="Mk3_1" available="sc_18"><dialog-node id="Mk3_1"><text>La date pour rendre le projet arrive à grand pas. Unfortunately, you have to get back the paper owned by Maki. You gather your strength because /* affronter */ Maki will be difficult. \n You : I am here to get back your paper... \n Maki : What paper ? \n - The page you were supposed to do... you know for the project \n - I see... \n - .... \n - I am joking, of course I have it. Did you doubt about it ? \n</text><answer redirect="Mk3_2">A little bit</answer><answer redirect="Mk3_2">Of course !</answer><answer redirect="Mk3_3">Not once</answer></dialog-node><dialog-node id="Mk3_2"><text>Maki : Seriously ?! I told you to trust me... so trust me... \n - Remind me why are you here ? \n You sigh... How is it possible to have a memory so short...</text><answer redirect="Mk3_4">I am here for the project's page</answer><answer>I forgot...</answer></dialog-node><dialog-node id="Mk3_3"><text>Maki : You are the best partner ! Of course you were right to trust me. \n So now, do you want me to give you my project's page ?</text><answer redirect="Mk3_4">Yes I want it</answer><answer>No I do not want it</answer></dialog-node><dialog-node id="Mk3_4"><text>Mika finally give you his work. You read what he done and you are *kinda* impressed by it. You are happy by the fact that Maki was your project's partner because his work was great.</text></dialog-node>
			</dialog>
		</character>
		<character id="Woman" location="Secretary">
			<name>Secretary</name>
			<desc>She helps when she can the students...</desc>
			<dialog id="S_dia1" begin="S1_1" available="sc_11"><dialog-node id="S1_1"><text>You are going to enter in the secretary's office. What do you want to do ?</text><answer redirect="S1_2">Knock at the door before entering</answer><answer redirect="S1_10">Entering without knocking</answer></dialog-node><dialog-node id="S1_2"><text>Hello. How are you ?</text><answer redirect="S1_3">Great</answer><answer redirect="S1_4">Not so good</answer></dialog-node><dialog-node id="S1_3"><text>It is the perfect day to be happy. \n So tell me what can I do for you ?</text><answer redirect="S1_5">I need something</answer><answer redirect="S1_6">I just wanted to talk with you</answer></dialog-node><dialog-node id="S1_4"><text>Do not be worried, it will be better tomorrow. \n So tell me what can I do for you ?</text><answer redirect="S1_5">I need something</answer><answer redirect="S1_6">I just wanted to talk with you</answer></dialog-node><dialog-node id="S1_6"><text>Oh ! That's nice. You can come back whenever you need.</text><answer>Yes, sure</answer><answer>No, you won't see me again</answer></dialog-node><dialog-node id="S1_5"><text>I have several items in my possession. What do you need ?</text><answer redirect="S1_7">Health's points</answer><answer redirect="S1_8">Project's sheet</answer></dialog-node><dialog-node id="S1_7" execute="giveitem Hpts"><text>Secretary : As you ask politely, I give you these health's points. You will need them. \n You receive 40 health's points.</text><answer>Thank you</answer></dialog-node><dialog-node id="S1_8" execute="giveitem sheet"><text>Secretary : Oh I see. Why do you think I have a sheet for the project ?</text><answer>I heard it somewhere</answer><answer>It was written on a paper</answer><answer>It is just luck</answer></dialog-node><dialog-node id="S1_9"><text>Secretary : Well, I do not know if I will give it to you... You need to assist to the class first and then I will give it to you.</text><answer>Okay see you later</answer><answer>I do not want it</answer></dialog-node><dialog-node id="S1_10"><text>Secretary : What is these manners young man ! \n Do you really think that's a good behaviour ? I do not think so...</text><answer redirect="S1_11">Apologize yourself</answer><answer redirect="S1_12">Do not apologize</answer></dialog-node><dialog-node id="S1_11"><text>You apologize for your disrespectful behaviour. The secretary seems to relax a little bit. \n Secretary : Hmm... tell me why are you here and maybe I will help you ...</text><answer redirect="S1_5">I need something</answer><answer redirect="S1_6">I just wanted to talk to you</answer></dialog-node><dialog-node id="S1_12"><text>You do not want to apologize yourself. The secretary grins, she seems angrier than before. You think she won't help you for anything and maybe you are right... \n Secretary : First you come without knocking at the door and now you refuse to apologize for this. I won't give you what you want, come later !</text><answer>Leave the office</answer></dialog-node>
			</dialog>
			<dialog id="S_dia2" begin="S2_1_1" available="sc_17"><dialog-node id="S2_1_1"><text>Maki, your project's partner talked about a mystery key. You are now looking at it. A rumor says that the key is in the secretary's office. You knock at her door. The door slowly opens but everything is dark inside. She is not inside... \n What do you want to do ?</text><answer redirect="S2_3">Enter in the office</answer><answer redirect="S2_2">Come back later</answer></dialog-node><dialog-node id="S2_2"><text>You are frightening to enter in her office without her consent. If Maki were you, he would probably enter but you are too pure for this. You will come back later... when she will be available.</text></dialog-node><dialog-node id="S2_3"><text>You absolutely want this key and you know that it is in this room. So you have no choice. You quietly enter in the room and close the door behind you. The key could be everywhere and you do not know where to start.</text><answer redirect="S2_4">Start with the desk</answer><answer redirect="S2_5">Start with the drawer</answer></dialog-node><dialog-node id="S2_4"><text>You start with the desk but there is a lot of paper on it. It is really messy. You check every desk's *tiroirs*. Nothing... Suddenly, a shiny object take your sight. You bend over to have a better look and then with glistering eyes, you take delicately the key. * get the key *</text></dialog-node><dialog-node id="S2_5"><text>You start with the drawer. It contains thousand of books. Unfortunately your reseach seems unexisted... The only potential good things that you get was some private informations on your teachers... Maybe you could use them to get a bonus points on your project...</text><answer redirect="S2_6">Now check the desk</answer><answer>Give up the key's research</answer></dialog-node><dialog-node id="S2_6" execute="giveitem sheet"><text>The desk is no messy that you do not know where to start... There is no key amount the paper. You check every desk's *tiroirs*. Nothing... Suddenly, a shiny object take your sight. You bend over to have a better look and then with glistering eyes, you delicately take the key. * get the key *</text></dialog-node>
			</dialog>
		</character>
		<character id="Stranger" location="Amphitheater"
		           available="sc_12">
			<name>Unknown girl</name>
			<desc/>
			<dialog id="U_dia1" begin="U1_1"><dialog-node id="U1_1"><text>From upstairs, you have a good view on the amphitheater. You notice a girl sitting in the first row. You never saw this girl but you are a good person and you do want her to feel alone. You wonder why and decide to approach her. \n You : Hey are you okay ?... \n Unknown girl : Leave me alone, I do not need you ! I just want to be alone ! \n</text></dialog-node>
			</dialog>
		</character>
	</characters-list>
</game>